buzz99.com 2011-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Buzz99

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to your information that we collect and receive, it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or people we do not employ. At no time will we sell your information or release your personally-identifiable data without your permission. You can visit this Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself.

#### **Browsing the Site**

If you browse through the Site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide at some point to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: **IP address** , **the type of browser** and **operating system** used to access our site, the date and time you access our site, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your **** IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Site.

#### **Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies use non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to this website and other sites, such as the user IP address, pages viewed, date and time of your visit, and number of times you have viewed an ad _(but not your name, address, or other personal information)_ , to serve ads to you on this site and other sites that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

#### **Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie**

  * Google, as a third party advertiser, uses cookies to serve ads on this website.
  * Google can use the DART cookie to serve ads to you, the visitor, based on your visit to your sites and other sites you visit on the Internet.
  * Visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you would like more information about this see the [Google Privacy Policy **.**](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html)
